翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
我们要收购PGM公司
We're going for PGM.
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
我们利用杠杆资金 吃掉皮尔斯
We leverage up and eat Pierce,
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
这样 对于桑迪和斯图威来说 我们就太大了
we're too big for Sandy and Stewey to come for.
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
大家都喜欢这个计划吧
We all like this?
压制　Jason肖
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
和这个家族联系 确实有一个他们喜欢的重量级人物
Contact with the family did have one heavyweight they liked.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
弗兰克
Frank.
没有你 情况就不一样了
It's not been the same without you.
变得更好了
It's been better.
恐怕卡罗丽娜有坏消息 关于那本传记
Carolina has bad news about the biography.
那个作家 任何跟她访谈的人都会完蛋
The writer, anyone who speaks to her,
我会弄死他们
they're dead to me.
你和娜奥米·皮尔斯是闺蜜 对吧
You're pals with Naomi Pierce, right?
你想通过娜奥米来促成交易吗
You want to use Naomi to broker a deal?
恭喜你猜中了
Bingo.
皮尔斯家族知道了你要收购他们的消息
The Pierce family got word that you were on maneuvers.
我们得马上回去
We need to back right off.
有人在阻止收购皮尔斯
Someone spiked Pierce.
是你们哪个猪猡干的
Which one of you boars did it?
地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor.
-你在隐藏什么  -你在...
-What are you hiding? -What are you--
是罗曼
It was Roman.
他接到了娜奥米·皮尔斯的电话
He took a call from Naomi Pierce.
罗曼 你是个白痴
Roman, you're a moron.
谁支持我收购皮尔斯
Who backs me on Pierce?!
他们都反对
They're all against it.
我们要收购它
We are going after it.
我要怎么做才能让他认真对待我
How do I get him to take me seriously?
那就参加管理培训计划
Do the management training program.
从底层做起
Ground floor.
皮尔斯的总裁瑞亚·贾雷尔 她可以帮我们
Pierce's CEO, Rhea Jarrell, she can help us.
好了 是时候让你参与进来了
Okay, it's time to bring you in.
瑞亚
Rhea.
还是我 肯德尔·罗伊
It's Kendall Roy again.
希望我这样做不会显得太怪异
I hope this isn't getting weird.
...嗯 我只是想跟进一下你的进展...
...Yeah, I just, wanted to check in and...
弗兰克给我的印象是 和你联系是一件很酷的事
Frank gave me the impression it was cool to make contact.
希望我们能...
Just hoping we can...
嗯 我们今天能如约见面
Yeah, we can make this happen today.
很高兴联络你
Would just be good to connect.
好了 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
怎么样
So?
-什么  -第一天进公司
-What? -First day in.
-这更像是实情调查  -当然 不过还是很兴奋 不是吗
- It's more of a fact finder. - Sure, but it's exciting, no?
这就像你和你爸终于承认
It's like you and your dad have finally admitted
你们彼此之间有多喜欢对方 对吧
how much you're into each other, you know.
现在你可以...你懂的 虽然不太一样 不过你可以发威了
And now you can... You know, not this, but now you can bang.
...那么你目前对雷文海德是什么看法
...so what's the current thinking on Ravenhead?
雷文海德 继续关注他 年轻的天才 人不错
Ravenhead, stick with him. Young talent, nice guy.
你爸爸喜欢他 而且
Your dad likes him, and,
他是我们最受欢迎的主播之一
he's one of our most popular anchors.
是的 当然 但他是法西斯主义者吗
Yeah, sure, but is he a fascist?
嗯 这个词内容量很大哦
Well, that's a very loaded word.
你看过这个视频 汤姆
You've seen the video, Tom.
他和法西斯分子在一起
He's right there with the fascists.
那是很久以前了
It was a long time ago.
他对政治很感兴趣 他被邀请去参加一个会议
He was interested in politics, he gets invited to a conference,
他很兴奋 他不知道自己会...
he's excited, he has no idea who he's--
自己会和谁坐在一起
who he's sitting on a panel with,
这一切听上去似乎很合理
It's all perfectly plausible.
是的 这个解释似乎很合理 但这是真的吗
Yeah, it's plausible, but is it true?
小西 得了吧 谁21岁的时候没干过出格的事
Shiv, come on. Who wasn't a bit salty when they were 21?
他现在成熟了 他住在康涅狄格州
He's grown up now. He lives in Connecticut.
他疯狂地喜欢尼克斯队 他...他是个可爱的家伙
He's crazy about the Knicks, he's-- he's a lovely guy.
而且...他的演示显得更年轻
And-- and his demo skews younger.
他妈的这是怎么回事
The fuck is this?
雷文黑德的粉丝
Ravenhead fanboys.
早上好 混蛋们
Morning, assholes.
那是我们的混蛋
Those are our assholes.
好吧 技术上来讲 他们是你的混蛋
Great. Well, technically, they're your assholes.
大声说出来 清晰说出来
Say it loud, say it clear,
欢迎雷文黑德来这里 大声说出来 清晰说出来...
Ravenhead is welcome here! Say it loud, say it clear...
好的 现在这些是谁的混蛋
Okay. Now who are these assholes?
情况可能会变得很糟糕
This could get ugly.
你能想象有人真的在这里清理过吗 汤姆
Can you imagine if someone actually cleaned up here, Tom?
带着他妈的净化的热情
With a cleansing fucking zeal?
像玛丽·波平斯一样努力吗[电影"欢乐满人间"女主角]
Like Mary Poppins with a hard on?
不 像我一样 或者你
No, like me. Or you.
继     承
第 二 季  第４集
就是这个了 祝我好运
This is it. Wish me luck.
好了 我正在退出地球的大气层
All right. I'm exiting Earth's atmosphere.
王子正在离开宫殿
The prince is departing the palace.
六个星期后见
See you in six weeks.
如果我没回来 派点暴徒来救我
If I don't come back, send goons.
他们可能会把我献祭给他们的神灵
They may sacrifice me to their gods.
欢迎来到管理培训课程
Welcome to management training.
日程安排
Itinerary.
谢谢 好的
Thanks. Okay.
欢迎各位
Welcome, everyone.
恭喜你们所有人被选中来到这里
Congratulations to all of you for being selected to be here.
这非常令人兴奋 你们都兴奋吗
This is very exciting. You all excited?
-是啊  -好的
- Yeah. - All right.
在这段短片之后 我们会让大家出去
After this short video, we'll get you out
穿着公仔服体验下公园
for a taste of the park in costume.
好了
Okay.
韦斯达·罗伊科集团是一个家庭
Waystar Royco is a family.
一个跨越四大洲的大家庭
a family that spans four continents,
五十个国家 三个部门
fifty countries, three divisions:
娱乐 新闻和度假村
entertainment, news, and resorts.
我们致力于提供一个可以容纳世界的网络
Working together to provide a net that can hold the world,
或者将它推向下一次冒险
or catapult it forward to the next adventure.
加入韦斯达·罗伊科
Joining Waystar Royco,
你就加入了世界上最具活力的
you're joining one of the most dynamic
新闻与娱乐公司之一
news and entertainment companies in the world.
感受它
Feel it.
韦斯达的多样性和骚扰政策
Waystar diversity and harassment policy.
韦斯达·罗伊科一直致力于发展一个宽容
Waystar Royco has worked hard to develop a tolerant
与尊重并存的工作环境
and respectful workplace.
公司坚定承诺
The company is strongly committed
根据有效的要求做出雇佣决定
to making employment decisions based on valid requirements,
而不考虑种族 肤色 宗教
and without regards to race, color, religion
或宗教信仰 年龄 国籍
or religious creed, age, national origin,
祖先 性别 性别认同
ancestry, gender, gender identity,
性别表现...
gender expression--
他妈的视频怎么回事
What the fuck happened with the video?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我的镜头被砍了 我和一些卫星
I've been cut. It's me and some satellites
出现了 大概 三秒钟
for, like, three seconds.
我会查清楚的
I'll find out.
这不是什么大不了的事 格丽
It's not a big deal, Gerri.
我不在乎我出现多少分钟
I don't care how many minutes I get,
只是在乎这其中传达的信息
it's just the message it sends.
当然 我知道了
Sure thing. I get it.
那 上课上得怎么样
So, how is it going?
太棒了
Amazing.
我正在返璞归真 这是我的白色专辑[披头士乐队的巅峰之作]
I'm stripping back to basics. This is my White Album.
这在美国是很可怕的事情吗
Is it very horrible in America?
不 这很光荣 是的
Yes. It's glorious, yeah.
不管多少抗菌凝胶
No amount of antibacterial gel
都无法从我身上抹去我的美国梦
is gonna be able to wipe the America off me.
这对你有好处 罗曼
This is good for you, Rome.
我知道 我要变成熟 成为一个真正的小男孩
I know. I'm gonna grow up and become a real little boy,
并学习一个鸡蛋的价格
and learn the price of an egg,
像个正常人一样和我的女朋友电话性爱
and do phone sex with my girlfriend like a normo.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
勇敢点 好吗
Just be brave, okay?
好的 老妈
Yes, Mommy.
欢迎来到大家庭
Welcome to the family.
是啊 终于来了
Yeah. Finally in.
那 都有些什么事情要处理
So, what's on the slab?
代理权争夺战的战术这些屁事
Proxy battle tactical shit.
很高兴有你的公关想法助阵
Good to have your PR thoughts.
经销商
Distributors.
核实雷文黑德的情况 老莫的葬礼
Check in on Ravenhead. Mo's funeral.
那么 我应该在哪里办公 那边吗
So, where should I base myself? In there?
不是那里 那是肯德尔的位置 他有自己的办公室
Not there. That's Kendall. He has his office,
但是 代理权争夺战期间 我们保持密切联系
but on the proxy battle, we keep close.
有道理
Makes sense.
我们会给你安排个位置的 就这附近哪里
We'll find you somewhere. Something nearby.
好的 随便你 我移动办公
Yeah. Whatever. I'll float.
那 每一天都以一杯香槟开始吗
So, every day begins with champagne?
让我们...遭受重创 并且在坦桑尼亚购买一家矿业公司吧
Let's...get hammered and buy a mining company in Tanzania.
有何不可呢
Why not?
爸
Dad.
是时候了
It's time.
小西
Shiv.
吃了饭以后注射这针黄色的
With food, this yellow one.
我以为是琼在负责爸的药物问题呢
I thought Joan was on his medication.
琼漏了一剂
Joan missed a dose.
所以 在我们有一个可靠的体系之前...
So, just till we have a system that we can rely on...
你妹妹是为了并购计划过来的
Your sister's just in for the day.
是吗
Yeah?
好的 随便你
Okay. Whatever.
-只是来观察观察  -很酷
- Just to observe. - Cool.
只是来观察什么
Just to observe what?
这不是什么大不了的事 肯
It's not a big deal, Ken.
对 当然 好点子 不错 观察
No, sure. Good point. Good, observation.
露西 你能给小西找个办公的地方吗
Lucy, can you find Shiv somewhere?
我要和小肯做准备了
I'm gonna prep with Ken.
20分钟
Twenty minutes.
你能搞定吗
You good?
德克火鸡 我们可以拍张照吗
Dirk Turkey! Can we get a photo?
当然
Of course!
-拍照时间  -对不起
- Picture time. - Excuse me.
你能为我们拍张照吗
Can you take a photo for us?
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
好的 我们来拍吧
All right, here we go.
-好的  -你好
- Right. - Hello!
我猜你们两个没有经常做爱吧
So I'm guessing you two aren't fucking much?
-对不起 你说什么  -你应该回家把这问题想明白了
- Excuse me? - You need to get home and figure this shit out.
这种状态很可悲 我的朋友
This is a sad state of affairs, my friend.
这个女人需要的满足感你显然提供不了
This woman needs satisfaction that you are clearly not providing.
感谢你的到来 祝你在公园玩得开心
Thanks for coming. Enjoy the park.
刚刚是什么意思
What was that?
我说"去你妈的"
I said "gobbledy go fuck yourself!"
所以 我只是好奇 格雷格
So, I'm just curious, Greg.
做汤姆的行政助理是什么意思
What does it mean being executive assistant to Tom?
好吧 我...我执行各种目标导向的任务
Well, I-- I perform a variety of target-oriented tasks,
并密切关注交易流程
and keep close to the deal flow,
-以及...  -有点像...
-and... -Sort of, kind of like a--
像农场工人吗 帮他挂外套 你需要给他挤奶吗
like a farm hand? Clip his coat? Do you have to milk him?
不 我只是 低着头
No. I just, keep my head down,
一直搅动拿铁 你知道吗
and keep the lattes flowing, you know?
你是一个聪明的小家伙 你知道吗
You're a smart cookie, you know?
我们应该谈谈
We should talk.
格雷格 等你调完情了
Greg! When you're done flirting,
可以帮我端杯拿铁吗 谢谢
can you latte me, please?
嗬 再见 董事会的领主和大人们
Ho! Farewell, lords and masters of the board.
真正开会的时间到了
Time for the real meeting.
这么火辣的实习生是谁啊
Who's the hot intern?
当我不在这儿 我只是在观察
I'm not here. I'm just observing.
罗曼 我会自杀的
她来了 瑞亚 我们接到她了
She's coming. Rhea. We got her.
优秀
Excellent.
-这事是真的吗  -据我了解是这样
-It's real? -As I understand it.
皮尔斯家族不知道她要来 所以...
Family doesn't know she's coming, so...
对吧 我的意思是 为什么要骗老太太 除非...
Right? I mean, why lie to the old lady, unless...
你真的准备操她
you're down to fuck?
现在 这事就我们三个
Now, this is, us three.
-就我们负责这个事  -是的 这家人信任她
-We're the group on this -Yeah. The family trusts her.
你要是能说服她 就意义重大了
You get her on board, that's huge.
她可能是我们的科里奥兰纳斯[莎士比亚历史悲剧中的人物]
She could be our Coriolanus.
他最后叛变了
He switched sides.
你知道吗 你干嘛不拿着你的借书证 然后...
You know, why don't you take your library card and...
滚他妈蛋呢
fuck off?
那...
So...
第一个议题是什么
What's first?
雷文黑德
Ravenhead.
我在这件事上被地毯式轰炸了
I'm getting carpet bombed on this.
联邦通信委员会 反诽谤联盟
FCC, ADL.
皮尔斯的新闻满天飞 而反法西斯行动也出现了
Pierce News is all over it, and Antifa has turned up.
我们不能在那里装架水炮吗
Can we not get a water cannon down there?
你知道 给他们他妈的来个淋浴降降火
You know, give 'em a fucking shower,
该死的狗杂种
fucking animals.
我相信警察已经控制住局势了
The police have it under control, I believe.
嗯 是的 但是我认为粉饰太平很不明智
Well, yeah, but I don't think it's smart to sugar-coat it.
对我来说 "泛美网络被围困了"
To me, "ATN under siege."
-那才应该是我们的路线  -赞同 支持
-That's our line. -Agreed. Endorsed.
而且 我已经成功地说服了广告商
And, I've managed to talk the advertisers down off the ledge,
所以我认为 我们只要渡过危机就可以了 对吧
so I think we just weather the storm, right?
好吧 问题是 外界要求我们发表评论
Well, the problem is we've been asked to comment,
因为 很显然 马克...
because, apparently Mark...
记录显示 他是在"鹰巢"结的婚
Records show that he got married at the Eagle's Nest,
希特勒在巴伐利亚的静养所 下面的小教堂
Hitler's retreat in Bavaria. A chapel below.
天啦
God.
忽略这个
Ignore that.
-当她不在这  -他的经纪人向我保证 这只是个巧合
- She's not here. - His agent assures me that it was a coincidence,
他们当时在那个地区度假
they were on vacation in the area.
是的 好吧 也他妈的太巧合了
Yeah, well, fuckin' big coincidence.
这对我们来说是个灾难吗
Is that curtains?
我想他完蛋了 对吧 我们直接把他扔了算了
I think he's toast. Right? We just toss him.
拜托 不要场外指导
Come on. No coaching from the sidelines.
不 我没在这里
No. I'm not here.
对 我忘了 你没在这里
Right. I forgot. You're not here.
嗯 你说什么 肯
Well, what do you say, Ken?
够了 悉德 你怎么看
Enough. Cyd?
我们不想解雇他 他很有吸粉能力
We don't wanna fire him. He's a big draw.
如果我们这次屈服了 那下一个轮到谁
And if we cave to this, then who's next?
汤姆 把他查清楚 查个底朝天
Tom, check him out, turn his guts inside out.
但是 不 我们支持人才  让雷文黑德留下来
But nah. We back talent. Ravenhead stays.
康纳 你准备好了吗
Connor, you ready?
你还好吗 亲爱的 我知道你对死亡的看法
You okay, honey? I know how you are about death.
♪ 祝老莫死亡日快乐 ♪
♪ Happy deathday to Mo ♪
-♪ 祝老莫死亡日快乐 ♪  -好吧 不是很难过
-♪ Happy deathday to Mo ♪ -Okay, not so sad.
对我来说这是个大好机会 宝贝
This is a big opportunity for me, baby.
-是吗  -是啊
-Yeah? -Yeah.
竞选筹资
Campaign financing.
老莫认识很多高净值人士
Mo knew a lot of high-net-worth individuals.
我要在那里积极运作 认识一些有钱人
I'm gonna work the room, meet some wallets.
整个教堂会塞满哭泣的自动取款机
The whole church is gonna be stuffed with weeping ATMs.
对了 玛西娅打过电话来
Right. So, Marcia called.
玛西娅 她打电话给你吗
Marcia? She called you?
是啊 她想让我跟遗孀谈谈
Yeah. She wanted me to talk to the widow,
看看老莫跟传记作者说了些什么
see what Mo told the biographer?
好 这样很好
No, this is good!
他们让你参与他们恶心的小阴谋
They're involving you in their disgusting little stratagems.
-对  -这意味着他们喜欢你
-Right. -It means they like you.
走吧 准备好在老莫的葬礼上挤点眼泪吧
Come on. Let's get ready to shed a tear at Mo's funeral,
也叫作"淘金记"
AKA the gold rush.
光是想想筹款这事 我就兴奋得勃起了
I'm getting a donor boner just thinking about it.
很可爱啊
That's cute.
格雷格 有什么事
Greg. What's going on?
乔纳 打声招呼
Jonah, say hi.
-格雷格  -乔纳
- Greg. - Jonah.
我在考虑把事情提升到一个新的水平
I'm thinking of taking things to the next level.
脚凳嘉年华
Footstool fiesta.
我们打赌 乔纳输了
We had a bet, Jonah lost.
有一天该轮到他对我做同样的事了
Be his turn to do it to me one day.
来吧
Come on!
-就...  -上啊
- Just... - Go ahead.
好啊 如果...如果我太重了 就告诉我
Yeah. Let-- Let me know if I'm too heavy.
好的 会说的
Yep. Will do.
那雷文黑德 在我和他见面之前
So, Herr Ravenhead. Do you have anything for me,
你有什么料给我
ahead of my meet?
...老实说 我一直在到处打听
...Honestly, I've been, been asking around,
但是没太多料
and not much.
我听说他给他的狗取了希特勒的狗的名字 好像是
I heard he named his dog after Hitler's dog, maybe.
小金金
Blondi.
这事可不好
That's not good.
不过 你知道 洛根喜欢他 美国人也喜欢他
But, you know, Logan likes and America likes,
而且"小金金"这个名字很常见
and "Blondi" is pretty common.
不 但我意思是 法西斯会议 纳粹婚礼 希特勒的狗的名字...
No, but I mean, fascist meeting, Nazi wedding, Hitler dog...
伙计 如果这是真的 他就完蛋了
Dude. If it's true, he's gone.
我的意思是 纳粹 可怕 对吧
I mean, Nazis, terrible, right?
纳粹吗
Nazis?
-是啊  -是啊
-Yeah. -Yeah.
是的 他们...他们带来的影响最坏
Yeah, they're-- they're the worst.
是的 没错 我们都讨厌纳粹 我们都讨厌悉德
Yeah, sure. We all hate Nazis. And we all hate Cyd.
对吧 乔纳
Right, Jonah?
如果我们看一下现在地球上可用的
If we look at the aggregate of all employment opportunities
所有就业机会的总和
available on Earth right now,
这个排名最高 2％
this is top one, two percent.
我们基本上是在天堂了
We are basically in heaven.
好吧 你还真不积极
Well, aren't you positive.
他们会打败你的 你有些什么经历 "挺不错的"先生
They'll beat that out of you. What's your story, Hunky Dory?
我吗 我是个谜
Me? I'm an enigma.
你不能把我归类 我在那里 然后我离开了
You can't pigeon-hole me. I'm there, then I'm gone.
我在理性上很滥交 但在文化上很保守
I'm intellectually promiscuous, but culturally conservative,
我努力工作 但我不努力玩耍 我轻松地玩耍
I work hard, but I do not play hard. I play easy.
-你为什么要努力玩耍  -好问题
-Why would you play hard? -Good question.
那你现在做什么
And what is it you're doing right now?
我在潜伏 像一个休眠的病毒
I'm lurking. Like a dormant virus.
把我的时间留在迈尔斯堡度假村
Biding my time in the Fort Meyers resort,
但是 我被各种各样的敌人阻碍
but I'm being stymied by a variety of enemies
他们嫉妒我的才华
who are envious of my talents.
-很显然  -我叫布赖恩
-Obviously. -Brian.
是啊 罗恩 罗恩...罗克斯通
Yeah. Ron. Ron... Rockstone.
当然 伙计 非常可靠的名字
Sure, man. Very solid name.
在代理声明方面
In terms of proxy statements,
我不确定你需要看多少资料
I'm not sure how much you need to see.
嗯 也许把所有资料都拿给我看
Yeah. Maybe just show me everything.
是吧 因为 那可是很多材料
Yeah, because, that's a lot of material.
我可以处理得很快
I can process pretty quick.
之后 也许我们和爸爸坐下来
And after this perhaps we sit down with my dad,
过一遍公关策略
and go through PR strategy?
他今天下午不在
He's unavailable this afternoon.
因为什么 要在屁股上注射猴子腺体吗
Because what? Monkey gland butt injection?
是啊 类似这样的事情
Yeah. Something like that!
把他的头发都炸掉了
Getting his hair blown out.
是的 他的下午都废掉了
Yeah, his afternoon is greyed-out.
然后就是老莫的葬礼
And then there's Mo's funeral.
卡罗丽娜知道吗
Does Karolina know?
科林做了他该做的事吗
Has Colin done his thing?
好的
Okay.
-谢谢你 杰西  -好的
-Thank you, Jess. -Okay.
-什么事  -没什么
-What was that? -Nothing.
当然
Sure.
好吧 杰西 然后肯德尔
Well, Jess, so Kendall.
还有卡罗丽娜...
And Karolina...
所以 这是面向公众的事 但是 科林也有份
so public-facing. But Colin, too?
那就肮脏了
Grubby.
爸爸在开秘密会议
And Dad's in a secret meeting,
而我在这里无所事事
and I'm in here with a coloring book.
到底发生了什么事 格丽
What's goin' on, Gerri?
也许你应该和你爸爸谈谈
Maybe you should talk to your dad.
拜托 是我啊 发生什么事了
Come on. It's me. What's happening?
是肯德尔
It's Kendall.
怎么 他又把老头子激怒了吗
What, is he huffing Sharpies again?
入店行窃
Shoplifting.
他在偷东西吗 偷什么
He's stealing? Stealing what?
我相信是糖果和电子烟液
Candy and vape fluid, I believe.
他偷电子烟液吗
He's stealing vape fluid?
不会吧 他可以买下整个行业啊
What? He could buy the entire industry.
嗯 有人和他谈过吗 他被停职了吗
Well, is someone talking to him? Is he suspended?
我们正在处理这事 以免把他牵扯进来
We're cleaning it up without getting him involved.
好啊 那样他就能"得到"教训了
Good. That'll teach him a lesson.
对不起 这他妈怎么回事
I'm sorry, what the fuck?
这家伙到底有几条命
How many lives does this guy have?
洛根希望保持低调
Logan wants to keep it down low.
只是 只是想了解一下 看看你进展如何
Just, wanted to check in and see how you're doing.
很好 有意思 是啊
Good. Interesting. Yeah.
嗯 那就好 那 你怎么样
Yeah, great. So, what's goin' on?
你还好吗
How are you?
你的下一步是什么
What's your next move?
你在考虑进入媒体吗 比如 这里 或者其他地方
Are you thinking media? Like, here, or somewhere else?
某个分部
Division?
嗯 这样的 我也不知道 但是...
Yeah, you know, I don't know, but...
-我..我必须告诉你吗  -不 当然不用
-I-- Do I have to tell you? -No, sure.
听着
Listen.
-我知道你工作丢了  -是我自己辞职的
-I know you lost your job. -I walked out.
好吧 无所谓 都没关系
Okay, whatever. It's all good.
我只是...嗯 我不知道 我...
I just-- Yeah, I don't know. I...
-很高兴见到你  -好啊
-It's good to see you. -Cool.
也许我应该来得再勤快点
Maybe I should come in more often.
肯 你的事
Ken? Your thing.
-她在路上了  -好的
-She's en route. -Okay.
-什么事  -没什么事
- What's that? - It's nothing.
小西 这...这不...这不是什么事 好吗
Shiv, it's-- it's, it's not a thing. Okay?
只是我不能说
I just can't say.
没关系 肯 去干你的秘密任务吧
That's fine, Ken. Do your secret shit.
你好像把我错当成你的竞争对手了
You seem to be mistaking me for someone you're in competition with.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗯 外面挺让人兴奋的啊
Well, that was exciting.
就像把埃及艳后裹在地毯里偷偷送进来一样
Smuggled in like Cleopatra in the carpet.
是啊 对不起 搞得这么秘密
Yeah. Sorry for the cloak and dagger.
瑞亚·贾雷尔
Rhea Jarrell.
你肯定是俄狄浦斯·罗伊[被命运拨弄而弑父娶母的底比斯国王]
And you must be Oedipus Roy?
我逗你呢
I'm teasing.
-对  -我们是走这边吗
- Right. - Are we this way?
是的 这里
Yeah, over here.
外面的骚动 我很抱歉
Sorry about the commotion outside.
瑞亚·贾雷尔 洛根·罗伊
Rhea Jarell, Logan Roy.
爸爸 瑞亚·贾雷尔
Dad, Rhea Jarrell.
真高兴你能来
It's lovely to have you.
请坐吧
Please, have a seat.
请问你喝点什么
Now, can I get you something to drink?
水就好 谢谢
Just some water, thanks.
景色真美
Quite a view.
自由女神
Lady Liberty.
那 会议议程只是为了解决 你知道的
So, the agenda of the meeting is just to sort of, you know,
看看我们如何才能更好地合作
check in on how we can all better work together
保护身处恶劣环境中的记者
to protect journalists in hostile environments,
-以及其他任何领域的...  -是的 是的
- and any other areas-- - Yeah, yeah,
谢谢你的封面故事[掩人耳目的说法]
thank you for the cover story
但我们没必要来这套了
but we don't need to bother with all that.
我们知道你又对收购感兴趣了
We know you're interested in an acquisition again,
而且 我带来了一条消息
and, I have a message.
是的
Yeah.
这条消息将代表皮尔斯家族
The message would be, on behalf of the Pierce family,
以及他们私有了150年的
and the media organization that it's privately owned
媒体机构
for 150 years,
这条消息将是典型的和谐 微妙的表达方式
the message would be a typically balanced, nuanced,
目的是表明"滚开"的态度
and objective "fuck off".
非常微妙
Very nuanced.
这是整个家族的看法吗
And is that the view of the whole family?
他们团结一致吗
They're united in that?
好吧 我不参与宫廷阴谋
Well, I don't involve myself in the palace intrigue,
但总的来说 他们家族知道你在追求什么
but overall, the family knows what you're after,
而且他们没兴趣
and they're not interested.
那我在追求什么
And what am I after?
你又在演奏你最喜欢的曲子 是吧[明知故问]
Your playing your favorite tune again, no?
只不过这一次 我会认为 一些天才银行家
Only this time, I take it some genius banker
已经说服了你 将豺狼拒之门外的唯一方法
has convinced you that the only way to keep the jackals out
是利用杠杆将你自己变大 直到你大到无法被人吞并
is to leverage yourself until you're too big to take down.
那 我可以向你保证 这样描述我们在这里做的事情
Well, I can assure you that is not a fair characterization
-一点也不公正  -听着
- of what we're doing here. - Look.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
皮尔斯吗 一般来说吗
The Pierces? In general?
-谁知道呢  - 那 还是有价格吧
-Who knows? -So there is a price?
我只能说 在目前这个时间点
All I can say is that at this point,
他们的立场是 不感兴趣
the position is they're not interested.
你呢 你怎么看
And you? What do you think?
我认为他们是了不起的保管员
I think they're amazing custodians.
所以 其实你对谁做你的主人并没有立场
So you don't have a position on who your owner is,
因为 如果你选定立场 这样可能会
because that would presumably affect things,
-对事情产生影响  -我是总裁
-if you weighed in? -I'm a chief executive.
我听命于董事会 我只是一个执行工具
I take my orders from the board. I'm a mere tool.
无论如何 我希望这次不会太令人失望
Anyway, I hope this hasn't been too disappointing.
这很有趣
It's been fun.
你知道吗 我想要皮尔斯
You know, I want Pierce.
但是 只有快点完成收购对我才有意义
But it only works for me fast.
非常快
Very fast.
所以 请留下来 一起吃午饭吧
So, please, stay. Have lunch.
我的胃很娇惯
My tummy is delicate.
我们在皮尔斯真的只吃普利策[讽刺泛美没有拿过什么普利策奖]
We really only eat Pulitzer over at Pierce.
你吃吧
You eat.
我会...
I'll...
待五分钟 然后和来的时候一样偷偷溜出去
stay for five and skulk out the way I skulked in.
好了 各位 既然你们都为下一个练习
Okay, everyone, now that you've found a partner,
找到了自己的搭档
for this next exercise,
我希望你们都能在新的游乐设施或景点方面
I'd like you all to come up with some ideas
想出一些点子
for new rides or attractions.
然后 把它精炼成一句广告语
And then, work it up into a pitch,
给大家展示一下 好吗
and we're gonna present to the group, okay?
这是什么 他妈的学校吗 我们现在要搞推销吗
What is this, fucking school? We're pitching now?
要是我们不鸟她怎么样 如果我什么都想不出来怎么办
What if we fuck it? What if I can't think of anything?
我没有准备任何东西 你知道这个吗
I don't have anything prepared. Did you know about this?
这很酷 听上去是个很棒的练习
This is cool. Sounds like a great exercise.
你他妈的根本没明白
You have no fucking understanding
这是怎么回事 对吗
of how this works, do you?
就像 这个 现在这个 这是末尾淘汰
Like, this, right here? This is a rank and yank.
要么晋升 要么出局
It's fucking up or out.
这是一场他妈的穿越雷区的死亡游行
This is a death march through a fucking minefield.
好了 好了 来吧 人们喜欢什么
Okay, well, come on. What do people like?
普通人喜欢什么
What do everyday people like?
做...普通 我他妈怎么知道
Do-- Everyday? How the fuck should I know
普通人都喜欢些什么
what everyday people like?
我喜欢在城堡订一间套房
I like booking out a suite at the Chateau,
然后用鼻子吸食精炼舍曲林[中枢神经系统药物]
and snorting purified sertraline
远离那些还不知道自己会成为妓女的女人
off women that don't know they're prostitutes yet.
这爱好很有趣 罗恩·罗克斯通
Interesting hobby, Ron Rockstone.
好吧 普通人喜欢什么 你喜欢什么
Well, what do the normos like? What do you like?
-我吗   -是啊
-Me? -Yeah.
好吧
Okay,
我喜欢和我的侄子库珀和克拉克共度时光
I enjoy spending time with my nephews, Cooper and Clark.
我徒步旅行 我有几款高端竞赛无人机
I hike. I have several high-end racing drones.
我的天啦 别说了
My God, stop.
请勿见怪 但是 哇
No offense, but, woo.
恐怖怎么样 真正的恐怖
How about terror? Like, actual terror.
就像VR体验一样 但是 是那种
Like a VR experience, but like,
"我他妈真的会死 " 就像战争一样
"I'm actually gonna fucking die." Like war.
比如 我们把你放进其中一艘登陆艇上
Like, we put you in one of those landing crafts,
然后你准备去海滩了...
and you're about to hit the beach...
-是的  -诺曼底 你知道吗
- Yeah. - Normandy, you know?
从来没有人因为高估美国公众
No one's ever gone bust overestimating
对暴力的兴趣而被逮捕
the American public's interest in violence.
他妈的 说的是
Fuck yeah.
-把这狗屎写上  -行 是啊
-Write this shit up. -All right. Yeah.
马克 很高兴见到你 进来吧
Mark. Great to see you. Come on in.
我今天早上看了这个节目
I caught the show this morning.
很好 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
悉德呢
Where's Cyd?
她出去有点事 但是她...
She's out on a thing, but she's--
她觉得 我们俩谈谈会很不错
she thought it would be great for us to check in,
我...我是你忠实的粉丝
and I'm-- I'm a big fan.
谢谢你 谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
凯琳告诉我 你想要进行全面的检查
So Karyn tells me, you want the full colonoscopy,
伙计 不 不
Dude. No, no.
我觉得 我们都很清楚 这些事情多么愚蠢
We both know, I think, how dumb these things are.
你知道是怎么回事 这只是尽职调查
You know how it is. It's just due diligence
因为所有这些波澜 我能不能...
with all the turbulence, and, can I just--
只需要检查几项就好
just need to check a few boxes.
好的 好的 谢谢你对我的信仰
Sure, sure. Thank you for the show of faith.
不 不 不...没问题 好的 对
No, no. No-- No problem. Okay, right.
好了 这样做很尴尬 不过 我郑重声明
Okay, so this is embarrassing, but, just for the record,
我们有这...
and just so we have it...
你不是 也从未成为过
You are not, and have never been
美国纳粹党的一员 对吗
a member of the Nazi Party of the United States, have you?
拜托 汤姆 你认真的吗
Come on, Tom. You serious?
不是
Nope.
谢谢 就连问这个问题我都觉得不好意思
Thank you. Sorry to have to even ask.
还有...对了 希特勒的狗的事情
And-- Yes, the Hitler dog thing?
-好吧 狗的事情是胡说八道  -好 很好 我也是这么想的
-Okay, the dog thing's bullshit. -Great. Great. I thought so.
拼写不一样
Different spelling.
-好的 拼写不一样  -嗯
- Okay. Different spelling? - Yeah.
好了 还有这一个问题
Okay. And this other one that came up,
为了避免这个问题 你读过"我的奋斗"吗[希特勒的自传]
just to fend this off, have you ever read Mein Kampf?
...是的 我想 读过几次吧
...Yeah, couple of times, I guess.
读过几次
Couple times?
书里面有你第一次没有找到的复活节彩蛋吗
Are there Easter eggs in there you didn't get the first time?
听着 我...我只是...
Look, I'm-- I'm just--
我对那段历史感兴趣 好吗 汤姆
I'm interested in that period of history, Tom. Okay?
-略过  -略过 好的 谢谢
-I skimmed it. -Skimmed. Yeah. Thank you.
那...具体来说
And-- And what, specifically,
那段历史时期的哪些方面让你觉得有趣
do you find interesting about that period of history?
规模 悲剧
The scale. The tragedy.
是啊 是的 没错 确切的说 是哪个悲剧
Hell yeah. Yeah. Which tragedy, specifically?
欧洲的摧毁
Europe decimated.
七百万德国人
Seven million Germans,
两千万俄国人 五百万波兰人
twenty million Russians, five million Poles.
是啊 只是...我只是对下数字 马克
Yeah. Just-- Just checking the till here, Mark,
似乎你少算了几百万
and it seems you're short a few million.
-怎么回事  -他妈的怎么回事
- What was that? - The fuck was that?
-枪手 有枪手  -什么 他说什么
- Shooter. Shooter! - What? What did he say?
-他说什么  -枪手
-What did he say? -Shooter.
先生 请...请跟我来 是的 快跟我来
Sir? Please-- Please follow me. Yeah. Come on.
-我们有安全屋吗  - 我们有安全位置
-Do we have a safe room? -We have a secure location.
劳驾 劳驾 劳驾
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
劳驾 请给高管们让路
Excuse me. Executives coming through!
让开座间通道
Gangway!
道歉 好像有火警警报在响
Apologies. There seems to be a fire alarm sounding.
我们会找出原因 休息之后
We'll find out the cause of that and be right back with you,
马上回来
after the break.
请跟我来 各位 请...
Please follow me. Everybody, please--
-请跟我来  -这是怎么回事
- please follow me. - What's going on?
我们必须疏散
We have to evacuate.
天啦...我的天啦 他妈...他妈的怎么回事
God-- My God. What-- What the fuck?
大厅某个地方传来一声枪响
There was a gunshot from somewhere down the hall.
大楼里有枪手 我们认为他们进来了
Shooter in the building. We think they got in.
-我操  -其他人在哪儿
-Holy shit! -Where are the others?
洛根和小西在哪里
Where's Logan and Shiv?
-我们还在播出吗  -我不知道
-Are we still on the air? -I dunno.
是他们 对吧  反法西斯运动 或者是个疯子
This is them, right? Antifa? Or a maniac?
他们要来杀我们吗
Are they trying to come get us?
也许她出去了
Maybe she's gone outside.
也许我们应该试着出去
Maybe we should try to get outside.
-不 我们应该试着...  -这是...
-No, we should try-- -This is--
这是安全屋 好吗 这里就是避难室
This is the safe room, okay? This is the panic room.
-什么 这里怎么就安全了  -我们在这里很安全
-What? How is it safe? -We're safe here.
-冷静点  -这里只是个普通房间
-Calm down! -It's just a room!
怎么回事 发生什么了
What is this? What's happening?
我们会查清楚的 先生
We'll get on that, sir.
-我们只是想保证你的安全  -肯德尔在哪儿 他安全吗
-We just wanna get you safe. -Where's Kendall? Is he safe?
我们会找到他们的
We'll find them.
请开门
Open the door, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
小西 小西 谢谢 谢天谢地 感谢上帝
Shiv! Shiv, thank God! Thank God!
-你还好吗  -汤姆 发生什么事了
-Are you okay? -Tom, what's going on?
我不确定 我听说是疯子或者反法西斯运动
I'm not sure. I'm hearing crazies or maybe Antifa.
我们认为他们是冲着我来的
We think they were coming for me.
冲着你来的
Coming for you?
是的 也许吧 你知道 泛美网络的负责人 斩首行动
Yeah, maybe. You know, head of ATN. Decapitate.
等等 什么 谁说的
Wait, what? Who said that?
好的 好吧 你现在哪里
Okay, well, where are you now?
我和格雷格在安全屋里
I'm in the panic room with Greg.
好 太棒了 我现在过来那里
Okay, great. I'm coming there now.
好的 快点 注意安全 一会见
Okay, hurry. Be safe. See you soon.
你有武装吗
Are you armed?
我无权透露这些信息 先生
I'm not allowed to disclose that information, sir.
等等 如果...如果他是目标 也许单独给他一间安全屋
Wait. If-- If he's the target maybe he should get his own room.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好吗  -嗨 你好吗
-How you' doing? -Hi. How you doing?
你想要什么吗
You want anything?
-你想喝点水吗  -肯德尔在哪儿
-You want some water? -Where's Kendall?
-他安全吗  -嗯 我不知道
- Is he safe? - Yeah, I don't know.
什么情况 西沃恩
What is this, Siobhan?
-可能是反法西斯运动 他们认为是  -狗屎一坨
- Antifa maybe. They think. - Pieces of shit.
汤姆在哪里
Where's Tom?
你都听到些什么消息 一切都结束了吗
So what are you hearing? Is it all over?
事情似乎已经平静下来了 但老实说
Things seem to have calmed down, but honestly,
-我收不到任何信息 先生  -好的
-I can't get a read, sir. -Okay.
-有什么最新消息吗  -小西
- Any updates? - Shiv.
汤姆 你在哪儿
Tom, where are you?
-我和爸爸在一起  -什么 哪里
-I'm with Dad. -What? Where?
我...我在他妈的安全屋里
I-- I'm in the fucking panic room!
有两个安全屋吗
There's two panic rooms?
我想...我应该是进错了...我进错安全屋了
I think-- I'm in the wrong-- I'm in the wrong panic room.
好吧 只是...只要留在原地 这...
Well, just-- Just stay where you are. It's...
还有更多枪击吗
Is there more shooting?
不 没有 这里很安静 什么...你怎么样
No. No. It's all quiet here. What a-- How about you?
挺好 没事 真的有枪手吗
No. Good. Was there really a shooter?
我不...我不...还有谁和你在一起 小西
I don't-- I don't-- Who else is in there with you, Shiv?
-悉德在那儿吗  -没有
- Is Cyd in there? - No.
只有我和...
It's, just me and--
汤姆 我要挂电话了 注意安全 我爱你 再见
Tom, I should go. Stay safe. I love you. Bye.
什么他妈的 我们在烂房间里
What the fuck? We got the shit room!
这下完全说得通了
That makes total sense
因为这个安全屋感觉一点也不安全 好吗
because this safe room doesn't feel that safe. Okay?
我的意思是 这里是密封的吗
I mean, is that airtight?
或者...那是防弹的吗 这些窗户防弹吗
Or-- And is that bulletproof? Are these windows bulletproof?
我的意思是 他们可以在这里放毒气 对吧
I mean, they could waft gas in here. Right?
我觉得这种猜测于事无补
I don't think this speculation is very helpful.
我的意思是 这些是你在设计安全屋时
I mean, these are the things you think about
会想到的东西
when you're designing a panic room!
所以 我只是说说而已
So, I'm just saying.
人可以穿过那里
And a person can fit through there.
人绝对可以穿过那个窗口
A person can definitely fit through that window.
一个小个子 一个具有攻击性的孩子
A small person. An attack child.
好了 我要你带我去另一个安全屋
Okay, I need you to get me to the other safe room,
-真的那间 马上  -先生...
-the real one, right away. -Sir--
-你吃药了吗  -什么
-Have you taken your pills? -What?
-肯德尔有你的药吗  -我...我不知道
-Does Kendall have your meds? -I-- I don't know.
你想要点什么吗 你的血糖怎么样
You want something? How's your blood sugar?
-你想要点牛肉干吗  -也许吧 也许吧
-You want some beef jerky? -Yeah, maybe. Maybe.
-你还好吗  -我正要出去
- Are you okay? - I was on my way out,
而且 我不得不说
and, I have to say,
这似乎是一种非常极端的
this seems like a very drastic way
把我留在这里的方式
of keeping me on the premises.
来吧 这边 我们还在播出吗
Here, come, sit. Are we on air yet?
你知道有谁受伤吗
Do you know who was hurt?
正在等最新消息
Waiting on updates.
还有更多枪击吗
Any more shots?
瑞亚·贾雷尔 你好
Rhea Jarrell. Hi.
西沃恩 你好吗
Siobhan. How are you?
是啊 尽我所能地好了
Yeah. As good as I can be.
在报道我们了 在报道了
We're up. We're up.
...在15楼 我听到了警报声
...on the 15th floor, I heard the alarm
并被告知立即疏散
and was told to evacuate immediately.
我们匆匆忙忙地从14层楼梯冲下来
We were rushed down 14 flights of stairs.
我听到一位很明显非常紧张的工作人员说
I heard one staffer who was obviously very distressed
她听到一声枪响
saying she heard a single gunshot,
有人喊道 "有枪手"
and someone shouting, "Shooter!"
但是 大家都没事吧
Everyone's okay, though?
大家都没事 不过 很显然
Everyone's fine, but apparently
他们没办法参加葬礼了
they're not gonna make the funeral.
我想我们也不能离开 对吧
I guess we can't leave too, right?
我觉得不能离开
Didn't think so.
-嗨 谢谢你的到来  -嗯
- Hi. Thank you for coming. - Yeah.
我很抱歉爸爸没能在他去世之前
I'm so sorry that Dad didn't get to see him
-见他一面  -是的 他提出要见洛根的
-before he went. -Yeah, he was asking for Logan.
玛丽亚 请节哀顺变
I'm so sorry for your loss, Maria.
你知道 我从没见过老莫
You know, I never met Mo,
但我听说 他是个很好的人
but I heard that he was just a great guy.
-老莫  -你丈夫呀
- Mo? - Your husband?
我们很抱歉
We're so sorry.
他的名字不是老莫
His name's not Mo.
-什么 你叫他老莫  -他的名字叫莱斯特
-What? You call him Mo. -His name's Lester.
好吧 为什么每个人都叫他老莫
Okay, so why does everyone call him Mo?
-他的真名是莱斯特  -那是...
- His real name is Lester. - It was...
我想我有段时间没想过这个了
I guess I haven't thought about it for a while,
但这有点儿开玩笑
but it was kind of a joke.
-比如呢  -莫-莱斯特[molester: 性骚扰者]
-Like what? -Mo-Lester.
我觉得这个笑话很不好
I guess it wasn't a very nice joke.
-那他是吗  -天啦 不
- And was he one? - God, no.
只是 你知道...
Just, you know...
就像 瞎扯淡先生 放狗屁叔叔 这样的玩笑
Old Mr. Fiddlesticks, Uncle Meathands.
懂了
Right.
爸爸不让我们和他一起去游泳池
Dad wouldn't let us in the pool with him.
但是 你知道 那一代人...
But, you know, the guys of that generation...
那是一个不同的时代
It was a different time.
好了
Okay.
让我们在这个愚蠢的错误结束时搞定一个捐献人吧
Let's get a donor on the end of this boner.
我觉得政治行动委员会要攻击我了
I feel a PAC attack coming on.
这就像古老的爱情隧道 但更加时髦
It's like the old tunnel of love, but much hipper.
-你穿过它...  -瞎几把扯
-And you travel through it in... -Bullshit.
-...坐着形状像阴道的独木舟  -我们的点子秒杀他们的点子
-...canoes shaped like vaginas. -Our idea shits on their idea.
谢谢
Thank you.
不要他妈的拍手
Don't fucking clap.
好了 谁是下一个
Okay. Who's next?
他妈的 好了 行 不要搞砸了
Fuck. Okay. All right. Don't fuck this up.
不要搞砸了
Don't screw it up.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
-那 我们打算做的是...  -罗伊先生
- So what we tried to do is... - Mr. Roy?
...创造一个以成年人为中心的景点
...create an adult-focused attraction.
-好的 所以它被称为...  -罗伊先生
- Okay, so it's called... - Mr. Roy,
以防您手机上收到新闻提示
just in case you get a news alert on your phone,
泛美网络发生了一起事故
there has been an incident at ATN.
-我爸爸好吗  -有人暗示
-My dad okay? -It's been suggested
这可能是针对家族的联合攻击
it could be a concerted attack against the family.
您想让我们带您到一个更安全的地方吗
Do you want us to take you to a more secure location?
是的 我当然想了 快他妈带我离开这里
Yeah, of course I want that. Get me the fuck out of here.
走这边
This way.
非常混乱
There's a lot of confusion.
我们的记者目前被锁在大楼外面
We have reporters currently locked outside of the building.
我现在在控制室里面说话
I'm talking from inside the control room.
情况很不好 格雷格
This is not good, Greg.
他们只是想让我看起来像个胆小鬼
They're just trying to make me look like a coward.
我他妈躲在壁橱里
Hiding in the fucking closet
而她在枪林弹雨中跳着霹雳舞
while she's out there breakdancing through gunfire.
你跑得很快
You ran pretty quick.
你他妈也跑得很快
You ran pretty fucking quick, too.
我只是跟在你身后
I was just behind you.
每个人都在奔逃
Everybody was running.
这里的生命处于危险之中
Lives here are at risk.
但我们泛美网络不会被吓倒 我们决心实现...
But we at ATN will not be cowed. We're determined to fulfil...
看来没人受伤 枪手是一个人
Nobody hurt, it seems. One person.
听着 私下说一句 我认为我们安全了
Look, off the record, I think we're in the clear.
我们只需要再在这里坚持一会就可以了
We just need to hang out for a little while longer.
-等待确认  -好的
-Wait for confirmation. -Okay.
他妈的
Fuck.
闭嘴
Shut up.
汤姆 你觉得...你觉得现在聊聊时机合适吗
Tom? Do you think-- Do you think right now might be a good time for a little chat?
是吗 什么事 格雷格
Yeah? What, Greg?
我最近想了很多 而且
I've just been thinking a lot recently, and,
你知道...嗯 我不知道...
you know-- Yeah, I don't know....
我在这里的一个巨人的阴影之下
I'm in the shadow of a giant here.
也就是你
AKA you.
而且 你知道 如果我想成长
And, you know, like, do I wanna
我是不是需要一点阳光的照射呢
maybe catch some sunlight if I'm gonna grow?
比如 我可不可以抓住...抓住一个机会
Like, would it be okay for me to maybe take-- take a chance,
换到另一个部门去工作呢
and go to another department?
什么 我...我正在这里埋头苦干呢
What? I'm-- I'm digging in here.
是的 你是 我只是想知道
Yeah, you are. And I'm just wondering, like,
如果我去和其他人一起工作一下下
would it be maybe interesting for both of us
这对我们两个人来说可能都很有意思
if I go work with somebody else for a little bit?
抱歉
Sorry.
你...你是想和我分道扬镳吗 格雷格
Are you-- Are you attempting to break up with me, Greg?
这...这只是...
It's-- It's just--
伙计 泛美网络 人肉家具 还有...
Dude, ATN, human furniture, like...
口头攻击 身体羞辱
Verbal assaults, physical humiliations,
纳粹的事 枪手...
Nazi stuff, shooters...
我只是不喜欢这样...我只是...
I just don't love it like I-- I just--
我真的不喜欢这样 我想去探险
I don't really love it, and I wanna go explore.
然后我...我可以再回来
And then I-- And I can come back.
你懂吧
You know?
这可以就像是...就像是一个商业方面的开放关系
It could be like-- like a business open relationship.
这个感觉...
This is not a good...
不太好 格雷格 你给我的感觉不太好 你知道吗
feeling, Greg, that you're making me have, you know?
你能停止嘎吱嘎吱吗
Can you stop crunching?
当然 是的 对不起
Sure. Yeah. I'm sorry.
是的 我感觉...
Yeah, I'm feeling...
什么
What?
我只是...我觉得有点...你知道吗
I just-- I feel a little bit-- You know?
我知道 我知道 这只是一个想法
I know, I know. It's just an idea.
他妈的
Fuck.
-他妈的  -是啊
-Fuck. -Yeah.
他妈的
Fuck.
好了 汤姆 汤姆 汤姆
Okay, Tom? Tom. Tom.
-我们没事 我们没事  -我们没事了吗
-We're good. We're good. -We're good?
我们没事吗
We're good?
我他妈一点也不觉得没事 格雷格
It doesn't feel fucking good, Greg!
我们先...我们能...
Let's just-- Can we--
我不会让你这样对我的
I will not let you do this to me!
我不会放弃属于我的东西
I will not let go of what is mine!
什么...什么...什么...我做了什么啊
What-- What-- What-- What am I doing?!
别再往我身上扔了
Stop pelting me!
-他妈的 他妈的  -我...住手...住手...警卫
- Fuck! Fuck! - I was-- Stop-- Stop! Security!
-伙计们  -不 你退后 你给我退后
-Guys! -No, you back off! You back off!
这是管理层的事务
This is executive level business!
-好吗 不许动  -住手 汤姆 我们是朋友
-Okay? No! -Stop, Tom! We're friends!
你是我最好的朋友之一
You're one of my best friends!
你还好吗 儿子 当时你在哪里
Are you okay, son? Where were you?
嗯 我很好 爸爸 我没事
Yeah. I'm fine, Dad. I was fine.
看起来只有一个枪手
It looks like there was only one.
一个员工 泛美网络的栏目制片人
An employee. ATN segment producer.
-怎么 他突然暴怒了吗  -是自杀
-What, he went postal? -It was a suicide.
他在自己的办公桌前开枪自杀了
He shot himself at his desk.
科林 我需要多一点时间...
Colin, I need a little more time...
你还好吗
You okay?
各位 不好意思
Sorry everyone.
只需要再耽误大家20分钟
Just gonna need to keep you here another 20
我们再清查第三遍
while we sweep the third.
瑞亚 我们调回泛美网络的新闻频道 可以吗
Rhea, it's okay if we go back to ATN?
谢谢 可以的
Thanks, yeah.
...几分钟之内 他们现在正围绕着
...within minutes. They are now surrounding
这座建筑 在这里吸引观众
this building, and to catch our viewers up here
大约十分钟前 泛美网络的办公室里
about ten minutes ago, at least one shot was fired
至少响起了一声枪响 并伴随着尖叫声
inside the ATN offices, along with screams.
你还好吗
You doin' okay?
还好
Well.
我发现越来越难以向大家解释 为什么我要
I'm finding it increasingly difficult to explain to people
取消我的行程 还有 我现在人在哪里
why I'm canceling and where I am.
你今天下午在这里和我爸爸会面
And you were here having a meeting with my dad
所以...
this afternoon, so...
有意思
Interesting.
这只是...只是胡说八道
It's just-- Just nonsense.
你怎么会在这里
How come you're in?
你现在在这里工作吗
You work here now?
不 我只是...我们一家人共同拥有这家公司
No, I just... my family owns the joint.
我不清楚你是不是知道这一点
I don't know if you knew that.
...没有关于任何伤亡人数的消息
...no word on any number of casualties,
但我们确切地知道 至少开了一次枪
but we do know that there has been at least one shot fired.
不是你喜欢的风格吗
Not your favored style?
这个 要取决于你怎么看待新闻
Well, depends what you think news is.
是公用事业 还是娱乐选项
A public utility, or entertainment option.
实际上你可以两者兼顾 通知和参与
You can actually do both. Inform and engage.
好吧 它肯定充满了活力
Well, it's certainly full of vim.
充满了精力
Full of piss and vinegar.
我想 任何报价你都不会认真对待吧
I take it you're not taking any offer seriously?
实际上 小西 我们进行了富有成效的会面
Actually, Shiv, we had a productive meeting,
所以 还是让我和爸爸处理这件事吧
so maybe let me and Dad handle this.
抱歉 劳驾 笨拙的老小西
Sorry. Excuse me. Clumsy old Shiv,
穿着我的工作靴到处跺脚
stomping all over it in my work boots.
这次聊天很不错 不过我觉得 "难以接受"是最好的回答
It was a good chat, but I think "hard no" was the take home.
没有必要给这个会面定调
There's no need to put a name on it.
我也觉得并购不合适
Doesn't feel right to me either.
我们非常重视她的观点
And we take her view very seriously,
她多年的媒体业务经验
what with her years of media business experience.
我只是看不到并购的可能性
I just can't see it.
就像 对我而言 从文化上 政治上来说
Like, the thing for me is that culturally, politically,
你的运营 正是我们在投资组合中所缺乏的
your operation, it's exactly what we lack in the portfolio.
但我不知道业务方面是如何运作的
But I don't see how the business side works.
好吧 我会说商业合并效果很...
Well, I'd say the business synergies are--
很明显 你知道
are obvious, you know.
可以合并为一个法律 财务 分销
One legal, finance, distribution,
市场部门
marketing department.
我认为 是不相容的企业文化
I think it's the incompatible cultures
阻碍...阻碍了这笔交易
that-- that stink up the deal.
这方面...
On that...
我们确实有一件事要提
We did have one thing to mention that could,
可以解决这个问题
address that issue.
210亿美元
Twenty-one billion dollars.
好的 好吧 听着 我只是一个传声筒
Okay. Well, look, I'm a mere conduit.
好吧 也许你应该传传刚才的报价
Well, maybe you should conduit that.
你知道吗 我觉得问题在于
You know, I suppose the thing is,
这对皮尔斯家族来说 是企业感情的问题
it's an emotional matter for the Pierces.
金钱并非无关紧要 但是...但是 我该怎么...
Money is not irrelevant, but-- but, how can I put it--
去提出来呢
Relevant?
-不过...  -215亿
-Nevertheless... -21.5.
肯德尔 他...他有权利报价吗
Kendall. I-- Is he allowed to just say numbers?
-够吗  -这并不取决于我
- Is that enough? - It's not up to me,
你这样只是在跟自己竞标
so you're just bidding against yourself there.
听着 我是个人人都讨厌的毛茸茸的老混蛋
Look, I'm a hairy old bastard who everybody hates,
等等 等等
yadda, yadda.
但我他妈的爱死新闻和新闻人物了
But I fuckin' love news, and news people.
我们可以争论新闻的立场 但我会投资
We can argue the angles, but I will invest.
嗯 就目前的情况来看 这会花费
Well, it would take a hell of a lot of investment
大量的投资
from where things are.
-220亿  -天啦 肯德尔
- Twenty-two billion. - Jesus, Kendall.
他能这样报价吗 爸爸
Can he say that, Dad?
我的意思是 根本都不是钱的问题 对吧
I mean that's not even the issue, right?
-这个嘛...  -那...那问题是什么
- Well... - So-- So what's the issue?
编辑的独立性吗
Editorial independence?
如果缺了这个 我认为根本就没必要谈了
I don't think there's anything to even say without that.
嗯 好吧 有模型的 对吧 独立董事的模型
Well, okay, there are models, right, for an independent board.
先不管出价的问题 有设计好的结构
And forgetting the numbers, there are structures designed
确保目前的理念和目标
to ensure the current philosophical approach
受到保护
is protected.
好的 谢谢你 现在...
Okay, thank you. And now...
说到出价
remembering the numbers,
多少出价可以改变他们的心意
what would move the dial for them?
225亿
22.5?
现在 老实说 说话小心点 不然我会当真的
Now, honestly, be careful or I'll take you seriously.
好吧 如果业务方面行得通
Well, if the business side can work,
那我觉得 面对这个家族的论调可以是
then I guess one pitch for the family could be,
"韦斯达不是来强奸你的
"Waystar isn't coming in to fuck you,
而是要和你做爱 甜蜜得不能再甜蜜的无限的爱"
but to make sweet, sweet, Barry White-investment love."
美女被野兽拯救才是基调
Beauty saved by the beast would be the flavor.
我认为这说明你最积极的一面
I think it's telling that your most positive spin
听起来还是有点强奸的感觉
still sounds a bit rapey.
-你相信我吗  -我相信你吗
- Do you trust me? - Do I trust you?
真正的问题不是这个 爸爸
That's not really the issue, Dad.
我的意思是 你又不能活一万年
I mean, you're not gonna be around forever,
所以需要一个体系
so there need to be structures in place
-来保证...  -西沃恩 请你别插嘴了
-that are-- -Siobhan. Please.
这就是问题的症结所在
This is what it comes down to.
你知道 我们可以起草一份协议
You know, we can draw up some agreement
里面可以有这样那样的规定
with any number of provisions in it,
但是你知道 如果我想 我会找到绕开这些规定的方法的
but you know that if I want, I'll find a way round it.
所以 最后 还是同样的问题 对吧
So, in the end, it's a question, right?
如果我说 我不会乱动皮尔斯
If I say I won't fuck Pierce over,
我将保留品牌 他们的编辑 他们的人
I'll keep the brand, their editors, their people,
你相信我吗
do you trust me?
你会告诉他们相信我吗
And will you tell them to trust me?
因为当我说某件事情会发生的时候...
Because when I say something will happen...
那件事就会发生
that thing will happen.
我说得对吧 孩子们
Am I right, kids?
-对  -是的
- Right. - Right.
所以 你会告诉他们吗
So, will you tell 'em?
240亿 而且 我说话算话
Twenty-four. And they can trust me.
我...我和他一起的
I-- I'm with him.
所以 这是安全屋吗
So is this the safe room?
是的 显然 这里坚不可摧
Yes. Apparently it's impregnable.
好吧 他们宣布了获胜的广告语
Well, they announced the winning pitch.
宣布了吗
They did?
你是想吊我的胃口吗 布莱恩
Are you attempting to do suspense on me, Brian?
我们赢了
We won.
瞧瞧 真棒
Look at that. Great.
-你不相信我吗  -不是
- You don't believe me? - Nope.
在他们把获胜名单交给那个人之前 你不会正好知道
Do you happen to know who they were going to give it to,
他们要给的那个人姓什么吧
before they gave it to the name?
我觉得跟姓名无关
I don't think it was the name.
好吧 这话非常感人
Well, that's very touching,
但是 我他妈基本上就是这里的猫王了
but I'm basically fucking Elvis around here.
那 你想去核实一下吗
So you wanna go check?
是啊 是的 我们他妈的去核实一下
Yeah. Yeah, let's fucking check.
酷 好了 我马上回来
Cool. Well, I'll be right back.
宝贝 悼词用这个怎么样
Baby, how about this for the eulogy?
-"莱斯特感动了我们所有人 " - 好吧 不
-"Lester touched all of us." -Okay, no.
我认为你不应该发言
I don't think you should do your speech.
家里不会有别的人来参加了 我必须发言 我说了我会发言
No one else is gonna get here. I have to. I said I would.
宝贝 我觉得这样做对你的竞选来说真的很不好
Baby, I think it could be really bad for your campaign.
我的意思是 我刚刚在和那边的那些人聊天
I mean, I was just talking to those guys over there.
-狼群吗  -"狼群"
- The Wolf Pack? - "The Wolf Pack"?
是的 都是爸爸的老部下 当年打天下的时候
Yeah, Dad's old crew, back in the day.
天啦 好吧
Jesus. Okay,
他们和老莫之间的一些事情
some of the stuff that they got up to with Mo,
-你不会想扯上关系的  -当然不 我知道
-you do not want to be -associated with. -Sure, no. I know.
不过 情况还是很复杂 当时的时代不同
Still, it's complicated. It was a different time.
但是 那时候已经有法律了 不是吗
But it wasn't a time before they invented laws, was it?
我的意思是 如果这些屁事爆出来
I mean, what if this shit comes out,
而你还在公开赞美他 那怎么办
and you're on the record praising the shit out of him?
简直是一场噩梦
This is a nightmare.
为什么我不能和疯子关在一起
Why can't I be the one caught in a lockdown with a maniac?
-康纳  -你好 抱歉打断你们
-Connor? -Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
我是米歇尔·潘特西尔 我正在研究...
I'm Michelle Pantsil. I'm working on a study--
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我...莱斯特临死前 我和他谈了很多
I-- I spoke to Lester a lot toward the end.
他谈起你时总是那么深情
He always spoke so fondly of you.
你离我远点 大姐
I see you a mile away, sister.
怎么 你想挖掘我的宝箱
What, you want to dig through my treasure chest
挖一点以前的记忆宝石吗
for some previous memory gems?
不 我不想强迫任何人
No, I don't want to make anyone
做任何他们不想做的事
do anything they don't want to do.
如果你想在你的小书里印上一些字
If you wanna print something in your little book,
你可以印上以下几行
you may print the following line:
"康纳·罗伊从小
"Connor Roy was interested in politics
就对政治感兴趣"
at a very young age."
就是这
That's it.
康纳 康...这不是访谈
Connor. C-- This isn't an interview.
我们两个只是在葬礼上聊过天而已
We're just two people chatting at a funeral.
-好的  -很多人出席啊
-Fine. -It's a good turnout.
这是个很好的教堂 你不觉得吗
It's a nice church, don't you think?
我来告诉你 什么是很好的教堂
I'll tell you what a nice church it is,
"康纳·罗伊从小就对政治感兴趣"
"Connor Roy was interested in politics from a very young age."
好的 你知道拒绝和我谈话对你自己
Okay. You know you're not doing yourself any favors
没有任何好处吧
by refusing to talk?
有意思 所以我要补充一点
Interesting point, to which I would add:
"康纳·罗伊从小就对政治感兴趣"
"Connor Roy was interested in politics from a very young age."
我很期待听到你对莱斯特的致辞
I look forward to hearing what you have to say about Lester.
来吧
Come on.
好了 伙计们 我们都安全了
Okay, folks. We're all clear.
-他还在里面吗  -我不知道
-Is he still in there? -I don't know.
天啦
God.
你知道吗 格雷格 我知道...
You know, Greg, I know that...
我刚刚的行为一点也不酷 用瓶子 扔你
it wasn't cool, you know. The bottles, the attack.
对 感觉是不太好
No, it didn't feel great.
有时候 连我都不喜欢我自己 格雷格
I don't always like who I am, Greg.
好的 我明白了
Yeah, I get that.
但是 你难道不觉得 这对我来说可能是一个
But don't you think it might be just the right time
合适的向前发展的时机吗
for me to make a move?
你是认真的吗 格雷格
Seriously, Greg?
你很聪明 很有抱负 很忠诚
You're smart, you're ambitious, you're loyal.
我为什么要让你走 得了吧
Why would I let you go? Come on.
好吧 等一下 我有一件事 但我...我不是很愿意说
Okay, wait. I have a thing, but I-- I'm reluctant to say.
-你什么意思  -我...
- What do you mean? - I--
我只是...我有一些筹码 但我不是很愿意使用它
I just-- I have some leverage, but I'm reluctant to use it.
你知道 以免它给我们带来麻烦
You know, in case it sours things for us.
什么筹码 格雷格
What leverage, Greg?
我只是 ...
I just-- ...
好吧 我不是把它当作任何形式的威胁
Well, I'm not bringing this up as any form of threat,
但...
but...
那 你还记得
So, you know
之前你让我销毁的那些游艇的文件吗
when you had me destroy those documents at Cruises?
不记得
No.
好吧 我...我保留了...
Well, I-- I kept it--
我保留了一些
I kept a few of them.
以防我遇到麻烦 因为我很担心
Just in case I got in trouble, and 'cause I was worried
也许我正在销毁犯罪证据
that maybe I was destroying evidence of criminality.
你现在担心了啊
Did you now?
所以 就像 我不知道 可能是...
So, like, I don't know. Would it be...
我不想以一种感觉很可怕的方式
I don't wanna bring anything up to you
向你提出任何要求
in a way that feels, like, horrible,
但是 我现在跟你提这些 会不会不好
but would be bad for me to, like, mention those to you now?
你是在问我 能不能勒索我吗
Are you asking if you can blackmail me?
不...不 我...我不会...我讨厌那样做
No-- No, I-- I would-- I would hate that.
我喜欢你 只是 你懂的 前因后果
I like you, it's just, you know, context.
很好 我接受你的勒索
Very well. I accept your blackmail.
不 我不是在勒索你
No, I'm not blackmailing you,
-汤姆 不...  -但是 你这样就是勒索
-Tom. No-- -But you are, though,
-你这个臭狗屎 格雷格...  -我不是
-you piece of shit. Greg... -I'm not!
...我会给你升职 好吗
...I'm gonna accelerate you. Okay?
新头衔 加很多薪水 漂亮的新办公室
New title. Ton more money, nice new office.
你向上晋升 你可以扔掉你的少女胸罩了[低级职位]
You're moving up, you can throw away the training bra.
坐在大桌子旁边 这样你喜欢吗
Seat at the big table. You like that?
-可以吗 - 是的 我喜欢
- Yeah. - Yeah. I like that.
你他妈的...看看你这样子 那些文件 它们在哪里
You fucking-- Look at you. Where are they, those papers?
我永远不会说的
I'll never tell.
你是他妈的牛皮糖
You're a fuckin' slime ball!
-不是  -好样的
-No. -Attaboy.
因为我深信 无论是死亡或者活着
For I am persuaded that neither death nor life,
或者天使 或者公国 或者权力 或者存在的东西
nor angels, nor principalities, nor powers, nor things present,
或者未来的事 或者高度
nor things to come, nor height,
-或者深度...  -给你 我写了一份悼词
-nor depth... -Here you go. I did a pass.
我们看看能不能有点什么用
Let's see her try to make something out of this.
...都是出于神在基督耶稣里的爱
...from the love of God, which is in Christ Jesus,
-我们的主  -阿门
- our Lord. - Amen.
你好
Hello.
我作为人类的一员来到这里
I'm here as a fellow human
承认莱斯特 正如大家所知 已经过世了
to acknowledge that Lester has, as we know, passed on.
莱斯特是个男人
Lester was a man.
此外 莱斯特还是韦斯达公司
Also, Lester was an employee of the Waystar company
40年的老员工
for 40 years.
当一个人去世时 这很让人难过
And when a man dies, it is sad.
我们所有人有一天都会去世
All of us will die one day.
目前的情况是 莱斯特已经这样做了
In this case, it is Lester who has done so.
莱斯特活了78年
Lester was alive for 78 years.
没有活得更长久
But no more.
现在他已经去世了
Now he is dead.
莱斯特的妻子是玛丽亚 他们结婚15年了
Lester's wife is Maria. They were married for 15 years.
现在她很伤心
Now she is sad.
显然 他上周给一位好朋友发了电子邮件
Apparently he emailed a close friend last week,
谈到了霸凌文化
talking of a culture of bullying.
这里是新闻编辑室 不是他妈的幼儿园
It's a newsroom, not a fucking kindergarten.
再次表达我的哀悼
Again, condolences.
我自己也是组织负责人
As the head of an organization myself,
我只能想象你的感受
I can only imagine how you must be feeling.
-这是黑暗的一天  -未来会有很多反省
-It's a dark day. -A lot of introspection ahead.
也许我们下周可以再谈一次
Perhaps we could talk again next week.
谢谢你的热情款待
Thanks for your hospitality.
希望我们早日再见
Hope to see you soon.
好吧 如果没有见到 我们总是有安全屋的
Well, if not, we'll always have the panic room.
我会告诉他们你的出价
I'll let them know that number.
还有 他们可以相信我
And that they can trust me.
我会给他们诚实的评估
I will give them my honest assessment.
而且 如果你真的很认真
And, if you're really serious about
想接近这个家族 那就为自己着想
approaching the family, do yourself a favor.
给他们送一份友谊的大礼会比较好
A peace offering would be nice.
那个沃尔玛墨索里尼 雷文黑德 是他害得南·皮尔斯
That Walmart Mussolini who puts Nan Pierce
放弃自己的古典鸡尾酒会的 懂了吗
off her Old Fashioned, Ravenhead, yes?
干得漂亮 儿子
Well done, son.
干得好
Good work.
我他妈的厉害惨了 小塔
I fucking killed it, Tabs.
我把他们都赢了 你知道吗
I slaughtered them, and you know what?
他们嫉妒了 就是这么回事
They're jealous. And that's just all there is to it.
他们嫉妒了 话说 你怎么样
They are jealous. Anyway, how are you?
我很好 我 嗯 我正要进浴缸
I'm good. I'm, yeah. I'm about to get into the bath.
是吗 是啊 好的 你想要那啥吗...
Yeah? Yeah. Okay. Do you want to...
你想这样做吗 还是怎么着 我们要等六周才能见面
You wanna do this or what? We got like six weeks of this.
当然可以 好的
Yeah, sure. Okay.
那 我在浴缸里弄了很多泡泡
So, I am making the bath really sudsy.
是因为你很"脏"吗
Is that because you're a dirty one?
是啊 我是一个很脏 很脏的女孩
I am. I'm a dirty, dirty girl.
对 你就是
Yeah, you are.
而且我很想操你
And I would love to fuck you.
你想吗
Would you?
我现在很湿 等你来哟
I'm so wet for you right now.
不用...你不用说得那么具体
That's not-- You don't have to be so specific.
我很性感
I'm being sexy.
是的 只不过...你能不能别用你的声音那样
Yeah, it's just-- Could you not do that thing with your voice?
就是 呼吸急促 很不自然的那样
It's, like, breathy and unnatural.
我兴奋的时候就是这个声音 罗曼
That's what I sound like when I'm turned on, Roman.
我知道 只是...我只是不喜欢 你知道
I know, it's just-- I just don't like it, you know.
就像...我们就表现得正常一点 更像是
It's just, like-- Let's just be normal. More like,
"我想操你的下面"
"I wanna fuck you in the pussy."
好吧 好吧 我...我正准备进浴缸 但是 你知道的
Okay. Well, I was-- I was trying to get into it, but, you know.
好的 不 没事 你说得对 抱歉....
Okay. No, fine. You're right. Sorry....
我在操你 我...正在狠狠地操你
I'm fucking you. I'm-- I'm fucking you hard.
了不起
Amazing.
接下来你要做什么 你打算 我不知道
What are you gonna do next? You gonna, I don't know,
你打算换你的滤水器滤芯吗
change your water filter cartridge?
老他妈的天啊...我要到了 我要到了
Jesus fucking Christ-- I'm coming! I'm coming!
我到了 好极了 谢谢 万岁 再见 谢谢
I came. Yay. Thank you. Hooray. Bye. Thanks!
远处围观的人们开始感到绝望
A feeling of hopelessness has set in for those watching from afar,
这让很多人不禁去想
leading many to wonder,
向孩子们解释这场悲剧的最佳方法是什么
what is the best way to explain this tragedy to children?
皮尔斯新闻撰稿人大卫·斯坦顿加入进来了
Pierce News contributor David Stanton joins us.
大卫 首先 我们是...
David, first off, are we--
罗曼 又怎么了
Roman, what is it now?
你知道吗 我仍然很生气 他们没有给我拍
You know, I'm still pissed off they didn't give me
-任何好镜头  -你说真的吗
-any good footage. -Seriously?
他们把我当狗屎一样对待
They're treating me like I'm a piece of shit.
-你就是一坨狗屎  -去你妈的
-You are a piece of shit. -Fuck you.
我在这里发现了一颗钻石原石
I found a rough diamond out here
我想带他回来 尽快帮我查下他的情况
and I wanna bring him back with me. Fast track him.
此外 我们应该建我自己的游乐设施 婊子
Also, we should build my ride, bitch.
我会给你发邮件的 这是个天才点子
I'll email you. It's genius.
不 不 我们不会用你管理培训课程第一天
No, no. We are not building a ride that you came up with
想出来的点子建游乐设施的 罗曼
on your first day of management training, Roman.
好吧 你应该建的 我就是思想的喷泉
Well, you should. I am an ideas fountain.
你表现得就像一个过度兴奋的小男孩
You're acting like an over-excited little boy.
你知道吗 技术上讲 我是你他妈的老板
You know, technically, I'm your fuckin' boss.
去睡觉 罗曼 去睡觉
Go to bed, Roman. Go to bed,
把你所有的点子都打飞机打出来
and masturbate all your ideas out,
然后我们看看你明天还能有多兴奋
and let's see how excited you feel tomorrow.
好吧 也许 也许我会打飞机的
Well, maybe. Maybe I will.
也许我会开着免提放在枕头边
Maybe I'll just leave you on the pillow
这样你就可以听到我的才华喷涌而出了
so you can hear my brilliance cascading.
好吧 比这更糟的我都听过
Fine. I've heard plenty worse
你这不过是一个被宠坏的小子射精在自己身上而已
than a spoiled brat ejaculating on himself.
是吗 你确定吗
Yeah? You sure about that?
你知道吗 我现在就可以这么做
I could be doing it now for all you know.
好吧 开始吧 撸啊撸
Well, get going. Chop chop.
你这头恶心的小猪
You disgusting little pig.
你很可悲
You're pathetic.
你是个令人反感的小蠕虫 不是吗
You are a revolting little worm, aren't you?
是啊 是啊 对我是
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I am.
你这个小粘液小狗
You little slime puppy.
是 是的 我还是什么
Yes. Yeah, what else am I?
你是个恶心的家伙 罗曼
You're revolting, Roman.
是 是啊
Yes. Yeah.
药物方面只相信你吗
Only you can be trusted with the meds?
是啊 直到我们有一个可靠的体系
Yeah. Till we have a system going on.
我有个问题
So here's a question.
你和爸爸之间到底他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck is going on between you and Dad?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你抓住他什么把柄了吗 你在勒索爸爸吗
Do you have something on him? Are you blackmailing Dad?
不 我...我...我不知道...我们...我们只是...
No. I'm-- I'm-- I don't know-- We're-- We're just in...
这些天我们相处得很好而已
We're just in a good-- good place these days.
好吧 你和他之间有什么交易吗
All right. Do you have a deal with him?
他在汉普顿给你提条件了吗
Did he make you an offer in the Hamptons?
不 没有 小西 我们...没有交易
No. No, Shiv. There's-- There's no deal.
我向你保证
I promise you.
那是为什么 他为什么在保护你
Then what? Why's he protecting you?
保护我
Protecting me?
是的 吸毒 入店行窃
Yeah, the drugs, the shoplifting,
还有他妈的...并购出价
the-- the fucking-- the takeover bid.
嗯 我不确定你什么意思
Yeah, I'm not sure what you mean.
话说 你为什么这么关心
Anyway, why do you care so much?
你知道吗 这是...这怎么回事 发生了什么事吗
You know, what-- what is this? What's going on here?
-你加入进来了吗  -我们能不能聊聊
-You comin' in? -Can we just talk?
我他妈又不是傻子 我能感觉到你们之间的氛围
I'm not a fucking dummy. There is an atmosphere.
嗯 我不知道 他...他只是...
Yeah, I don't know. He's-- He's just...
也许 他是很关心我 不管是出于什么原因
Maybe, he's concerned about me, for whatever reason.
是吗 不管是出于什么原因
Yeah? For whatever reason?
你得去问他
You'd need to ask him.
你不能告诉我吗 你不能告诉我发生了什么事吗
You can't tell me? You can't tell me what's going on?
不能
No.
他妈的看着我
Fucking look at me.
小西 不会是我当接班人的
Shiv. It's not gonna be me.
好吧 你想告诉我原因吗
Right. You wanna tell me why?
过来 抱抱我
Come here. Give me a hug.
-过来  -抱抱你
-Come here. -Give you a hug?
你还好吗
You okay?
我只是想请你照顾我
I would just ask that you take care of me,
因为 如果爸爸现在不需要我了
because, if Dad didn't need me right now
我完全不知道...
I don't exactly know...
我该做什么
what I would be for.
你想再说说吗
You wanna talk some more?
我...我真的不能说
I r-- I really can't.
但是...
But...
谢谢你
thank you.
是的 接班人不会是我
Yeah, it ain't gonna be me.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠